ecopy.com 2009-12-23

# eCopy, Inc. - Document Imaging Software - Privacy Policy

This policy applies to the eCopy, Inc. Web site accessible through eCopy's home page located at www.ecopy.com. This policy does not apply to the Web sites of any subsidiary or affiliate company of eCopy or any other company that is associated with eCopy. Those Web sites, like any other Web site, may have their own privacy policies and eCopy encourages you to review the privacy policies of any of those sites that you visit. 

We (eCopy) understand the importance of providing you with information concerning the collection and use of data collected from you during your visit to our Web site. Our privacy policy is set forth below. This policy may be updated from time to time and we encourage you to check this page periodically for any updates. 

Definitions. Some helpful definitions of terms used in this privacy policy are:

Personal information is information that can be used to uniquely identify you personally. Examples of personal information include your name, mailing address, telephone number, e-mail address, and credit card number. 

Anonymous information is information that can not be used to uniquely identify you personally. Examples of anonymous information include your IP address, the type of browser software you use when visiting our site, the date and time you visit our site and what pages you viewed when visiting our site. 

**Collection and Use of Anonymous Information  
** You can visit our Web site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information to us. During your visit, we may collect certain anonymous information. For example, we may track the number of visitors to our Web site by logging Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. We may keep track of what pages are visited on our Web site so we can monitor the performance and usage of our Web site. Also, we may pay attention to what visitors do and do not use on our Web site in order to assess the effectiveness of our Web site and modify our content or design appropriately. Anonymous information may be used individually or aggregated with other anonymous information. 

**Collection and Use of Personal Information  
** We collect personal information about you only when you elect to provide such information to us, such as when you register to receive products or services, request additional information from us, enter a contest or promotion, or submit an e-mail to us. The information collected might include your name, company name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone numbers, etc. Any personal information collected will be used solely for the purpose(s) for which it was collected (for example, to send you additional information about our products or services that you requested) unless you indicate otherwise. The personal information you provide to us may be shared with other companies with which we have relationships in order to complete your request or provide you with the products or services which you have requested. We may also enlist a third party to collect, store, process and manage on our behalf any personal information you elect to provide to us. When we use other companies to perform services on our behalf, we will require that such companies protect your personal information consistent with this policy. 

In addition, from time to time, we may offer you the opportunity to receive information, products or services directly from a third party. If you elect to receive such items, we may share with such third party any of your personal information that was collected when you elected to receive such items. 

We may process or store your personal information in our databases located in the United States or any other country in which we do business. 

We may disclose personal information when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating the terms and conditions of our Web site or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property or anyone else that is being harmed by such activities. We may disclose personal information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for other governmental administrative, regulatory, or law enforcement purposes. 

**Use of Cookies  
** A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser software from a Web server and is typically stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. 

We may insert cookies on your computer and access those cookies. These cookies may be used to help you navigate through our Web site, to provide you with customized and personalized features, and to assist us in collecting anonymous information concerning usage of our Web site. 

Additionally, we may allow other companies to present advertisements on some pages on our Web site, and we may allow those companies to set and access their own cookies on your computer in connection with such advertising. Those other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not ours. 

Our Web site may contain links to third party Web sites. Our privacy policy does not apply with respect to those third party Web sites. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any of those sites that you visit. 

**Questions**  
If you have any questions about our privacy policy or the practices of our Web site [contact](http://ecopy.com/contact.htm):

eCopy, Inc.   
One Oracle Drive,  
Nashua, NH 03062, USA   
Attention: Marketing Department

Last Updated: July 1, 2006  

Back to Top

Back to Top
